Zhijiang Rongliang Wuxian Technology (Zhejiang) Co., Ltd. Zhejiang Yanhe Culture Technology Co., Ltd.
Lord Su, Mr. Shen, be careful.
This guy is crazy.
He bit a guard's hand just last night.
You are the lost only son of the Xu family,
Xu Lin.
Lost?
That was an abduction.
Abduction?
What exactly happened?
My Xu family
was a prominent family in Chang'an back then.
My father was an official in charge of salt and iron.
My mother was a lady from a noble family.
I was supposed to be a young master living in luxury.
But God is unfair.
Young Master,
slow down.
Young Master.
Young Master, Little Master,
where are you?
Young Master, where are you?
Young Master.
A-Cheng and the others are gone.
No one will disturb our playtime anymore.
Where is that fun thing you mentioned?
Young Master, I'm sorry.
They forced me.
Ah Cheng.
Is this a new game?
Help! Help!
How much?
Fifty taels.
Too expensive.
At least thirty taels.
He's a young master from a wealthy family.
Top-grade goods.
Deal.
From today on, you are mine.
I will teach you the most powerful martial arts.
Bone-Shrinking Skill.
From today on,
your bones will stop growing.
How else can you practice the Bone-Shrinking Skill?
Lift it.
If you want to be respected in public,
you must suffer in private first.
Lift it.
If you can't lift it, no dinner for you.
I miss my parents. I miss my old life.
Every day, I hoped they would come to save me.
But they didn't.
Nothing.
Only endless abuse.
From today on, your bones will stop growing.
How else can you practice the Bone-Shrinking Skill?
Good.
Very good.
Next,
is our finale,
the Heaven-Swallowing Rat Spirit.
Good.
Very good.
I'm sorry. They forced me.
Heaven-Swallowing Rat. Heaven-Swallowing Rat.
The name Xu Lin has long been forgotten.
They called me the Heaven-Swallowing Rat.
Over twenty years have passed.
I know I have long become a demon.
I hate the people who took away my name,
including the onlookers.
They are all guilty.
I burned them to death.
When I went back to find my parents,
I found out they were all dead.
There is no one left in my family.
I hate them.
I want to kill them all.
Revenge.
I returned all the suffering doubly.
Zhang Ergou and the others broke the law.
Why didn't you report to the officials?
Report to the officials?
I ran away from the theater,
and burned them to death.
Haven't you been wanting me all along?
While the three of them were living well.
Report to the officials?
Would you believe me
or them?
However,
there's still one thing left unfinished.
I hope you two
can uphold justice for me.
I will repay you generously in my next life.
Please speak.
I had a little playmate named Cheng.
I haven't been able to find him all these years.
He is the culprit behind this whole thing.
Help me catch him.
Cheng, who deceived you back then,
was sold to another troupe
by Zhang Ergou and his gang.
That troupe was even more cruel.
Cheng
died at the age of ten.
Let me out! Let me out!
Karma! Karma!
Xu Lin,
the yamen has issued a verdict.
You are sentenced to immediate execution for intentional homicide.
I have taken my revenge.
I have nothing left to long for in this world.
Save him.
Okay.
Wait.
It's too late.
Perhaps death
is a mercy to him.
This case is finally over.
If
Xu Lin hadn't been trafficked back then,
maybe now
he would be living a happy life.
Buddha says
there are one hundred and eight kinds of suffering in this world.
Observe others and examine yourself.
A gentleman should be careful when alone.
The way of the sage
is to save the world.
What's wrong with you today?
You want to save the world,
talking as if you were the emperor.
The rise and fall of the nation
is everyone's responsibility.